Now it's time for the test portion of cleaning data programmatically.
现在 到了编程数据清理的测试部分
Testing can be done immediately after coding each operation,
测试可在对各项操作编码后立即进行
like having one definition here,
比如给出一个定义
then converting that to code here,
然后将定义转换成代码
then immediately testing below which would change this header to code and test.
然后 立即进行如下测试 这可将此标题转换成代码 然后测试
But I'll separate the test portion out for this lesson.
但这节课 我将把测试部分分离出来
Okay. So testing can be done visually for simple fixes like modifying the column headers,
好 测试可肉眼进行 以便简单修复 比如修改列标题
aka our first issue here.
这也是我们的第一个问题
Slotting all non-descriptive and misspelled
找出所有非描述性和拼写错误的列标题
column headers and replacing them with full words.
并用完整单词替换它们
So to check visually, we'll just type in df_clean and view our DataFrame.
要进行肉眼检查 我们只需键入 df_clean 然后查看 DataFrame
And we'll scroll across.
滚动查看
Okay, application procedure.
好 application procedure (申请步骤)
That used to be application P so that is good we fixed that one.
以前是 applicationP 所以我们已经修复
And about company that used to be about C. So we're all good there too.
about company (公司信息) 以前是 aboutC 我们完成这一步了
But the other two column headers that we were trying to fix,
但我们尝试修复的其他两个列标题
required qualifications and job requirements,
即 requiredqualifications 和 jobrequirements
are hidden in the columns that Panda's collapses here.
隐藏在 Pandas 折叠的列之中
This is where programmatic testing comes in handy.
这就是编程测试派上用场的地方
Let's use Panda's info function to check out the columns that are hidden here.
我们用 Pandas 的 info 函数来检查隐藏在这里的列
Info is one of the programmatic assessments we covered in the assessed videos.
Info 是我们在评估视频中讲到的编程评估之一
And yes, okay, job requirements,
好了 jobrequirements 已修复
fixed, required qualifications, fixed.
requiredqualifications 已修复
Cleaning code will need to be tested programmatically just like this, in most cases.
大多数情况下 清理代码必须像这样进行编程测试
Let's use programmatic testing again to test that our second cleaning operation,
我们再次利用编程测试来测试我们的第二次清理操作
standardizing the ASAP start dates, actually worked.
标准化 ASAP 开始日期 真的奏效
In the quiz ahead, use Panda's value counts function
在接下来的测试题中 请使用 Pandas 的 value counts 函数
to verify that all of these similar phrases were converted to
来验证所有这些类似短语是否被转换为 ASAP
ASAP and let me know how many entries in that start date column are ASAP.
并告诉我 Startdate 列中有多少输入项为 ASAP